Artificial and Ephemera 060
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Hotels - Ritz-Carlton, Georgetown - Ritz-Carlton, Georgetown (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Hotels - St. James Hotel - St. James Hotel (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Hotels - Wardman Park Hotel - Wardman Park Hotel, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Hotels - Whitelaw Hotel, The - Whitelaw Hotel, The (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Hotels - Willard Hotel, The - Willard Hotel, The, 1913-ca. 1950 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Houses - Cedar Hill - Cedar Hill, 1922-1972 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  Frederick Douglass
- Houses - Chevy Chase - Chevy Chase (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Houses - Decatur House - Decatur House (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Houses - Dumbarton Oaks - Dumbarton Oaks, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Houses - Goodwin House - Specifications for building a dwelling house for J. R. Goodwin (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Houses - Henderson Castle - "Estate Sale of Valuable Paintings, Furniture, Furnishings and Objects D'Art Contained in Henderson Castle", 1935 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Houses - Oakview (Red Top) - Oakview (Red Top) (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - Alley Dwelling Authority, 1934-1944 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Accomplishments of the Alley Dwelling Authority as of June 24, 1936", 1936-06-24 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Alley Dwelling Authority Adopts Graded Rents, The", 1940-10-17 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Alley Dwelling Authority for the District of Columbia, The", 1941-05-02 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - Alley Dwelling Authority, Resolution NO. 1, The, 1940-07-18 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Development of the Inhabited Alleys of Washington", 1936-07-03 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Facts Regarding Application and Eligibility for Low-Rent Dwellings", 1940-09-30 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "National Public Housing Conference", 1936-01-25 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Properties and Projects of the Alley Dwelling Authority", 1942-10 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Public Housing in the District of Columbia", 1941-05 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Slum Reclamation and Rehousing", 1936-06-24 (Box 19, Folder 47)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Supplement to Management Resolution No. 1", 1940-07-30 (Box 19, Folder 48)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Supreme Court of the United States Upholds the Constitutionality of Public Housing" by John Ihlder, 1941-10-16 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Work of the Alley Dwelling Authority for the District of Columbia, The", 1935-12-07 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Housing - Alley Dwelling Authority - "Work of the Alley Dwelling Authority", 1938-04 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Housing - Alley Houses in District of Columbia - Alley Houses in District of Columbia, 1918-04-18 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Housing - Directory of the Inhabited Alleys of Washington, DC - Directory of the Inhabited Alleys of Washington, DC, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Inaugurations - Inaugurations - Inaugurations, 1937-1961 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Inaugurations - Barry, Marion - Barry, Marion, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Mayor of the District of Columbia
- Inaugurations - Bush, George H. W. - Bush, George H. W., 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Inaugurations - Carter, Jimmy - Carter, Jimmy, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Inaugurations - Cleveland, Grover - Cleveland, Grover, 1893 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Inaugurations - Clinton, William J. - Clinton, William J., 1993 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Inaugurations - Eisenhower, Dwight D. - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Inaugurations - Eisenhower, Dwight D. - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Inaugurations - Harding, Warren - Harding, Warren, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Inaugurations - Hoover, Herbert - Hoover, Herbert, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Inaugurations - Kennedy, John F. - Kennedy, John F., 1961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Inaugurations - McKinley, William - McKinley, William, 1897 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Inaugurations - McKinley, William - McKinley, William, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Inaugurations - Nixon, Richard M. - Nixon, Richard M., 1969 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Inaugurations - Obama, Barack H. - Obama, Barack H., 2009 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Inaugurations - Roosevelt, Franklin D. - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1933 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Inaugurations - Roosevelt, Franklin D. - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1937 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Inaugurations - Washington, Walter E. - Washington, Walter E., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Inaugurations - Williams, Anthony, A. - Williams, Anthony, A., 2003 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Invitations - America's New Millennium, The - America's New Millennium, The, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Invitations - Beauty and Fashion Show - Beauty and Fashion Show, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Invitations - Children's Apparel Show - Children's Apparel Show, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Woodward and Lothrop
- Invitations - Geophysical Exhibition - Geophysical Exhibition, 1957-04 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Invitations - Jackson Day Dinner - Jackson Day Dinner, 1940-01-08 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Invitations - Kenwood Golf and Country Club - Kenwood Golf and Country Club (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Land Records - Beall, Thomas (Deed) - Beall, Thomas (Deed), 1791-12-16 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Manuscript - needs rehoused
- Land Records - Carroll, Daniel (For Sale by) - Carroll, Daniel (For Sale by), 1811-01-12 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Land Records - Goodwin, John (Deed) - Goodwin, John (Deed), 1868-07-27-1868-09-04 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Land Records - Land Receipts - Land Receipts, 1810-1815-07-06 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Land Records - Onion and Butts (Deed) - Onion and Butts (Deed), 1901-02-13 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Land Records - Scmick, Valentin (Deed) - Scmick, Valentin (Deed), 1868-06 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Land Records - Towles, James (Deed) - Towles, James (Deed), 1868-08-27 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - 1905 - 1948 - 1905-1948 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - Childs, Thomas S. - "Supremacy of the Cross, The", 1913 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - Chipman, Norton P. - Chipman, Norton P., 1874-02-28 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - Clephane, Lewis - "Birth of the Republican Party", 1889 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - Community Institute of Washington - Community Institute of Washington, 1927-1932 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - National Theatre - National Theatre (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - Nearing, Scott - Nearing, Scott, 1940-1948 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - Newman Travel Talks - Newman Travel Talks, 1917-1936 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - Roosevelt, Franklin D. - "State of National Emergency, A", 1941-05-27 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Lectures, Speeches and Meetings - Stoddard Lectures, The - Stoddard Lectures, The, 1895-1896 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Libraries - Library of Congress - Library of Congress, 1867-2000 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Libraries - Library of Congress - Jefferson, Thomas Donation Letter, 1814-09-21 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  copy and negatives
- Libraries - Library of Congress - Publications - "History of the Library of Congress" by S. D. Wyeth, 1868 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Libraries - Library of Congress - Publications - "Practical Guide for Visitors, A", 1897 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Libraries - Library of Congress - Publications - "Library of Congress 1982, The", 1983 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Libraries - Public Libraries - Public Libraries, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Libraries - Public Library - Public Library, 1925-1977 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Libraries - Public Library - Central Library (Carnegie Library), 1903-1935 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Libraries - Public Library - Collections Department, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Libraries - Public Library - Music Division, 1935-1953 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "100 Years of History, 1896-1996" (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Early History of the Washington Library Company and other Local Libraries" by W. Dawson Johnston, 1903-01-12 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  from Records of the Columbia Historical Society
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Government Department Linraries: A Plea for Better Salaries" by George F. Bowerman, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Libraries in the District of Columbia" by W. I. Swamton, 1921-06 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Library Association of Washington City, Handbook", 1897 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  pages 13-32
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Public Library of the District of Columbia as an Organ of Social Advance, The" by George F. Bowerman, 1906-04-14 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Public Library of the District of Columbia Handbook and Work of 1920" (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Report of the Committee on Public Library of the Washington Board of Trade", 1894 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Second Annual Report of the Board of Trustees and First Annual Report of the Librarian of the Public Library of the District of Columbia for the Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 1899" (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Short Survey of Libraries in the District of Columbia from the beginning to the Civil War Period" by Anne D. Noble, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Short Survey of Libraries in the District of Columbia from the beginning to the Civil War Period" by Anne D. Noble, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Special Libraries", 1928-05 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Survey of the Library Needs of Citizens at Work", 1930 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Libraries - Public Library - Publications - "Theodore W. Noyes Portrait Presentation to the Public Library, Washington DC", 1922-02-16 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Libraries - Public Library - Washingtoniana, 1952-06 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  copy
- Libraries - Washington City Free Library - Washington City Free Library, 1895-1896 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Libraries - Washington Library Company - Washington Library Company, 1822-1858 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Liquor - Liquor - Liquor, 1898-1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Liquor - Excise Liquor Law - Excise Liquor Law, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Liquor - Hearings Before the Committee on the District of Columbia - Bill to Regulate the Sale of Intoxicating Liquors in the District of Columbia - Hearings Before the Committee on the District of Columbia - Bill to Regulate the Sale of Intoxicating Liquors in the District of Columbia, 1903 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Liquor - Instructions to Applicants for License to Sell Intoxicating Liquors - Instructions to Applicants for License to Sell Intoxicating Liquors, 1888-09-11 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Liquor - Reports - Reports, 1887-1893 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Liquor - Rules and Regulations Governing Issue of Liquor Licenses in the District of Columbia - Rules and Regulations Governing Issue of Liquor Licenses in the District of Columbia, 1893-03-16 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Liquor - Rules and Regulations Governing the Sale of Intoxicating Liquors in the District of Columbia - Rules and Regulations Governing the Sale of Intoxicating Liquors in the District of Columbia, 1910-04-01 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Lottery - Lottery - Lottery, 1826-1827 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Maps - Historic - Historic, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Maps - Mitchell Park - Mitchell Park, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Markets - Centre Market - Centre Market, 1825-06-30 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  contract agreement
- Markets - Eastern Market - "Eastern Market, A Living Market for a Lively Neighborhood" by the Third Grade Class of Two Rivers Public Charter School, ca. 2000 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Military - Corps of Engineers; Report of the Chief Engineers - Corps of Engineers; Report of the Chief Engineers, 1942-1952 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Military - United States Marine Corp - United States Marine Corp (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Militia - Corcoran Cadet Corps - Corcoran Cadet Corps, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Militia - Medal of Honor Legion - Medal of Honor Legion, 1893 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Militia - National Guard, 29th Division - National Guard, 29th Division, ca. 1925 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Militia - National Guard, District of Columbia - National Guard, District of Columbia (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Militia - National Guard, President's Troop - National Guard, President's Troop (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Militia - Washington Light Infantry Corps - Washington Light Infantry Corps, 1885 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Monuments and Memorials - Monuments and Memorials - Monuments and Memorials, 1909-1935 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Monuments and Memorials - Bolivar, Simon - Bolivar, Simon, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Monuments and Memorials - Braddock Rock - Braddock Rock, 1907 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Monuments and Memorials - Centennial Woman Suffrage Memorial - Centennial Woman Suffrage Memorial, 1876 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Monuments and Memorials - Daguerre, Louis Jacques - Daguerre, Louis Jacques, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Monuments and Memorials - Delano, Jane - Delano, Jane, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Monuments and Memorials - Douglass, Frederick - Douglass, Frederick, 1932-07-01 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Monuments and Memorials - Einstein, Albert - Einstein, Albert, 1960-01-28 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Monuments and Memorials - Eiriksson, Leifr - Eiriksson, Leifr, 1947-01-15 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Monuments and Memorials - Erickson, Leif - Erickson, Leif, 1944-1947 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Monuments and Memorials - Ericsson, John - Ericsson, John, 1926-05-29 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Monuments and Memorials - Farragut, David - Farragut, David, 1947-03-12 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Monuments and Memorials - First Division Monument - First Division Monument, 2002-05 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Monuments and Memorials - Flanagan, Edward - Flanagan, Edward, 1965-10-21 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Monuments and Memorials - Foster, Stephen - Foster, Stephen, 1953-01-05 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Monuments and Memorials - Franklin, Benjamin - Franklin, Benjamin, 1962-05-14 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Monuments and Memorials - Freedom Monument - Freedom Monument, 1960-07 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Monuments and Memorials - Galludet, Thomas H. - Galludet, Thomas H., 1966 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Monuments and Memorials - Gompers, Samuel - Gompers, Samuel, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Monuments and Memorials - Grant, Ulysses - Grant, Ulysses, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Monuments and Memorials - Jackson, Andrew - Jackson, Andrew, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Monuments and Memorials - Jefferson, Thomas - Jefferson, Thomas, 1904-1971 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Monuments and Memorials - Jones, John Paul - Jones, John Paul, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Monuments and Memorials - King, Martin Luther, Jr. - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 2006 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Monuments and Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham - Lincoln, Abraham, 1870-1925 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Monuments and Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham - "Development of Washington, The" by Glenn Brown, 1910 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Monuments and Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham - "Fry's Patriotic Story, The Lincoln Memorial" by Smith D. Fry, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Monuments and Memorials - Luther, Martin - Luther, Martin, 1886 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Monuments and Memorials - Marshall, John - Marshall, John, 1884-05-10 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Monuments and Memorials - Rochambeau - Rochambeau, 2004-07 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Monuments and Memorials - Roosevelt, Franklin D. - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1965-10-23 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Monuments and Memorials - Shepherd, Alexander Robey "Boss" - Shepherd, Alexander Robey "Boss", 1909-05-03-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Monuments and Memorials - Tropoli Naval Memorial - Tropoli Naval Memorial, 1815-12 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Monuments and Memorials - United States Navy - United States Navy, ca. 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Monuments and Memorials - Washington, George (Monument) - Washington, George (Monument), 1884-1885 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Monuments and Memorials - Washington, George (Monument) - "Foundation fo the Washington National Monument", 1873 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Monuments and Memorials - Washington, George (Statue) - Washington, George (Statue), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Monuments and Memorials - Witherspoon, John - Witherspoon, John, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Mosques - Islamic Center, The - Islamic Center, The, ca. 1957 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Moving Pictures - Moving Pictures - Moving Pictures, 1931-11 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Museums - Anacostia Museum - Anacostia Museum, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Museums - Anacostia Museum - 5th Anniversary Program, 1972-09-15 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Museums - Botanic Garden - Botanic Garden, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Museums - City Museum, The - City Museum, The, 2003-05 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Museums - Dumbarton Oaks - Dumbarton Oaks (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Museums - Frederick Douglass Center - Frederick Douglass Center, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Museums - International Spy Museum - International Spy Museum, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Museums - National Building Museum - National Building Museum, 2000-2005 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Museums - National Museum of American Art - National Museum of American Art, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Museums - Octagon House - Octagon House, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Museums - Smithsonian Institution - Smithsonian Institution, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Museums - Smithsonian Institution - "Brief Guide to the Smithsonian Institution" (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Museums - Smithsonian Institution - "Geologist's Paradise, A" by R. S. Bassler, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Music - Music - Music, 1927-1929 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Music - Contests - Contests, 1925 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Music - Library of Congress - Library of Congress, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Come on, Washington" (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Crab-Apple Blossoms", 1931 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Music - Musical Scores - "District of Columbia is My Hometown, The", 1951 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Hail to the Redskins", 1938 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Happy Am I", 1930 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Here's to Uncle Sam", 1941 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Home", 1924 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Hymn of Washington, The", 1927 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Jefferson Memorial at Washington", 1941 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Music Selected Expressly for the Grand Chorus of the District of Columbia in Commemoration of the Patriot Dead at National Cemetery, Arlington, Va.", 1870 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Music - Musical Scores - "National Monument, The" (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Music - Musical Scores - "President Lincoln's Funeral March", 1865 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Washington", 1920 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Washington", 1951 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Washington, Fair Capital", 1927 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Music - Musical Scores - "Washington Monument", 1948 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Music - Opera - Opera (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Music - Programs - Programs, 1948-1961 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Music - Programs - Armistice Day, 1939-11-11 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Music - Programs - National Theatre, 1920-02-17 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Music - programs - Smithsonian, 1974-03-11 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Music - programs - Washington's Second Music Week, 1922-05-28-1922-06-03 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Music - programs - Watergate Concerts, 1944-06-09 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Newsletters - Carlfax - Carlfax, 1933-09 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  Published by Call Carl, Inc.
- Newsletters - Goodwill, The - Goodwill, The, 1951-09 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  Published by Goodwill Industries Lettershop
- Newsletters - Greenway Citizen, The - Greenway Citizen, The, 1942-08-08 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  Published by the Greenway Apartment Community
- Newsletters - Montgomery Message, The - Montgomery Message, The, 1934-09 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  Published by the Montgomery Building and Loan Association
- Newspapers - National Intelligencer, The - National Intelligencer, The, 1832-11-27 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Newspapers - National Republican, The - National Republican, The, 1887-01-01 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Newspapers - Washington Correspondent - Washington Correspondent, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  pages 145-166 of "Without Fear or Favor" by Neil Macneil
- Newspapers - Washington Herald, The - Washington Herald, The, 1906-10-04 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Newspapers - Washington Star, The - Washington Star, The, 1930-1978 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Parades - American Legion - American Legion, 1966-08-30 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Parades - Emancipation Day - Emancipation Day, 1985-04-11 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Parades - Free the Scottsboro Boys - Free the Scottsboro Boys, 1933-05-08 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Parades - Grand Review - Grand Review, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Parades - Inaugurations - Inaugurations, 1901-1985 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Parades - Ku Klux Klan - Ku Klux Klan, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Parades - March for Victory - March for Victory, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Parades - March on Washington - March on Washington, 1963-08-30 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Parades - National Catholic Youth Day - National Catholic Youth Day, 1939-04-30 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Parades - National School Safety Patrol - National School Safety Patrol, 1966-05-16 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Parades - Publications - "Selected Parades in Washington Through 1959" by Mabel Sterns, 1985-05 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Parades - St. Patrick's Day - St. Patrick's Day, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Parades - Spring Festival - Spring Festival, 1932-05-01 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Parades - Vietnam War - Vietnam War, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Parades - Women's Suffrage - Women's Suffrage, 1914-1970 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Parades - World Series - World Series, 1947-06-03 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Parades - World War I - World War I, 1934-01 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Parks - Cabin John - Cabin John Park, 7 Miles From the White House: A Picture and Paragraph Story, Facts and Comments, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Parks - Glen Echo Park - Glen Echo Park, 2005-09-10 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Parks - Lafayette Park - "Trees and Shrubs of Lafayette Park" by Frederick V. Coville and O.M. Freeman, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Parks - Marshall Hall Amusement Park - Marshall Hall Amusement Park (Box 25, Folder 53)
- Parks - Meridian Hill - Meridian Hill (Box 25, Folder 54)
- Parks - National Capital Parks - National Capital Parks (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Parks - Pershing Park - Pershing Park, 1960-1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  Map needs unfolded
- Parks - Rock Creek Park - Rock Creek Park, 1916-10-11 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Parks - Rock Creek Park - "Rock Creek National Park" (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Parks - Rock Creek Park - "Some Reasons for the Preservation of Rock Creek Valley as a Public Park", ca. 1925 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Parks - Washington Luna Park - Washington Luna Park, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  cutter number G859 Y279 W
- Photography - Photography - Photography, 1948-2007 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Iraq War - Iraq War, 2003-2005 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - March on Washington Anniversary - March on Washington Anniversary, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 9)